top10vpn.com 2019-09-08

# Privacy Policy | Top10VPN.com

Welcome to Top10VPN’s Privacy Policy.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. If you use Top10VPN (“our Site”), you will be regarded as having read and accepted this Privacy Policy. If you don’t wish to be bound by what you read below, you shouldn’t use our Site.

Our Privacy Policy explains

  1. What information we collect and how we collect it
  2. How we use that information
  3. How to find out more about our policies

This is a very important policy page and we hope you will read it carefully.

###  **INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We do not ask you or anyone else to give us any personal information in order to use Top10VPN.

We do collect anonymised information to provide a better service to all our users – from improving our less popular pages to tracking the commissions that allow the site to operate as a free resource.

The only instance when we do collect personal information – specifically, your name and email address - is if, and only if, you submit a review of one of the VPN providers listed on our Site via the review submission forms we host.

We collect information in the following ways:

###  **User Reviews**

We give our visitors the option to leave us reviews of the VPN providers listed on our Site. By submitting your user review, you are agreeing to our Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy.

Personal data collection

Once you submit your review, the following personal information will be collected (exactly as submitted):

– Name  
– Email address

We ask for your email address to avoid bogus reviews being submitted. We will never share your data with any third-party, unless it is with the VPN provider you are subscribed to but only if you have entered into a prize draw they are running with us (see 'Data use and transfer' for more details). We will never contact you using the email address you provide us.

Data use and transfer

The reviews you submit may be published on relevant pages of our Site. The published review will also include your Name, as submitted to us.

We also occasionally collect user reviews as part of prize draws. We will only contact the winner(s) of the prize draw in order to award the prize.

If we are jointly running a prize draw with a VPN provider, we will share the winners’ names and email addresses with that same provider for the purpose of awarding the prize. Upon specific request from the provider, we may also share with them the email addresses of all participants that entered their prize draw. We will only transfer your submitted personal data outside of the EEA if:

  * you have won a prize, and
  * the VPN provider awarding the prize is located outside the EEA

Under no other circumstance will your name and email address be used or shared by Top10VPN.

Data retention

Your Name and email address, exactly as submitted to us, will be stored in our secure reviews database for as long as your review is published on our Site.

Data deletion

If you wish to have your review removed from our Site, and your name and email address removed from our Reviews database, please email your request to editorial@top10vpn.com.

Please note, the request must originate from the email address submitted as part of the review, as proof of authenticity.

###  **User Testing**

We occasionally ask our visitors to apply to take part in testing new features of our website. As part of the application, visitors will be asked to provide their email address via a submission form.

Not all applications are successful and the email addresses submitted by all unsuccessful applicants will be purged once the recruitment phase is complete.

If you have been selected to participate in one of our tests, we will only email you instructions on how to carry out the test(s), and the agreed reward once the test(s) has been adequately completed.

Your email address will be stored securely until the testing period is over, at which point they will be purged.

We may also ask if you would like to be contacted to participate in future tests. If you give us consent to do so, your email address will be added to our ‘User Testing’ email list.

If at any point you wish to have your email address removed from this list, and permanently purged from our records, please email your request to [hello@top10vpn.com](mailto:hello@top10vpn.com).

###  **Site Analytics**

Every time anyone visits our Site, we collect anonymised information about that visit. Like most big websites, we do this through Google Analytics software to better understand how people use our site. While we do not use Google Analytics to collect any personally identifying information (such as name or address), we do collect the following kinds of information:

  * The pages you visit on Top10VPN.com
  * How long you spend on each page of our Site
  * How you got to our Site
  * What kind of device you were using
  * Your home country and browser settings such as language

We also sometimes use other third-party analytics tools, such as Hotjar, that collect information about how you interact with our Site, such as what you click on and the parts of the page you spend most time on.

We use this information to better understand our customers and their needs in order to improve our service.

This information is anonymized and cannot be tied back to any individual. Nevertheless, we never share it with anyone outside of PrivacyCo unless specifically required to by law.

This anonymized analytics information is stored behind secure log-ins that can only be accessed by PrivacyCo employees using their official credentials.

###  **Cookies and similar technologies**

Like most websites, Top10VPN puts small files (known as ‘cookies’) onto your computer to collect information about how you browse our Site.

You can read our [cookie policy](https://www.top10vpn.com/cookie-policy/) for a detailed breakdown of the types of cookie we use and why we use them.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not, and by allowing us to earn commissions.

A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you. You can choose to accept or decline cookies through your browser settings. Look at aboutcookies.org for detailed guidance about how to do this.

We may implement third party advertising or other content on the Site that may use clear gifs or other forms of web beacons, which allow the third party content provider to read and write Cookies to your web browser in connection with your viewing of the third party content on the Site.

Additionally, we may implement third party buttons (such as Facebook “like” or “share” buttons) that may allow a third party to collect information about you through their browser Cookies, even when you do not interact with the button.

Information collected through web beacons and buttons is collected directly by third parties, and Top10VPN does not participate in that data transmission. Information collected by a third party in this manner is subject to that third party’s own data collection, use, and disclosure policies.

##  **LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES**

Top10VPN contains links to other websites.

This privacy policy only applies to this website, and doesn’t cover other sites that we link to. If you go to another website, read the privacy policy on that website to find out what it does with your information.

##  **CHANGES**

We may, from time to time, update this Privacy Policy to reflect any changes to our privacy practices in accordance with changes to legislation, best practice or enhancements to Top10VPN. We will let you know what these changes are by posting them to this page, but it is your responsibility as a user to make sure that you are aware of them, by checking for any changes on a regular basis. Changes will become effective as soon as they are posted.

##  **HOW TO CONTACT US**

Top10VPN.com is owned and operated by PrivacyCo. If you have any questions about our cookies or this policy, please contact us at [hello@top10vpn.com](mailto:hello@top10vpn.com) and we will get back to you within two working days.

PrivacyCo  
Fourth Floor  
33 Great Sutton Street  
London EC1V 0DX

 **Last updated:  28/08/2019**
